(phone rings)
- Welcome to Drop as Aligned, hello.
(laughing)
- Hey, Andy, hello and welcome to Drop as Aligned.
- This is exciting, we're back.
- We're back, we haven't been gone.
We've been gone for compilations, but--
- It's been a month since we've been sat around the table
together like this.
- Yeah, I think maybe even six, wait, it's been a long time.
- Yeah.
- The inbox, genuinely now, is bulging.
- Are you saying that every other time you said it's been bulging,
it's not genuinely been bulging?
- No, it doesn't, it's all time.
- No, well, you guys needed a confidence boost, I thought.
You know, the inbox has been anemic every other week.
I've said it, but this time, it's bulging.
So we're going to a six-week lieuritation on Drop as Aligned.
I hope that's all right with everyone.
We're going to do one thing every six weeks.
- As if, Andy.
- This is your favorite part of the job.
- I have genuinely missed it.
I've been setting a home doing Drop as Aligned
with my teddies and stuff.
There's been a nightmare, and they're not nearly as funny
as you guys.
- Right, and let's introduce ourselves now.
I'm Andrew Hunter Murray, this is James Harkin
and Dan Shriver.
- Hello.
- We're here to talk about the emails that you've been sending.
You've been sending if you're listening
or watching to this.
- Yeah.
- If you're listening to or watching this, sorry.
Here are your emails.
- How did the teddies find your intros?
(laughing)
- They said they needed a bit of work.
- Yeah, they've asked to be taken to the charity shop.
(laughing)
- Right, get yourself off the hook.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
- Wind.
- We've had some corrections on the matter of wind.
- Okay.
- Peter Munroe, who I believe works in wind.
(laughing)
- In it.
- He works in the "Mung the Wind."
- Oh yeah.
- He's a renewable guy.
- When did we talk about wind?
Was it windmills at the R.I.?
- It was windmills at the R.I.
- Right, okay.
- He just points out that wind turbines,
they operate in wind speeds of 25 meters a second,
but above that, they're locked down.
And I think we said they might break,
but they don't actually,
they are designed to survive hurricane force winds
of 110 meters a second without breaking.
- Okay.
- So I think then breaking is very unusual.
- It is, is Peter saying that they've never broken due to wind?
- No.
- No, I don't think he would say that.
- He's not saying they've never broken due to wind,
but he says normally when they're turned off,
it's because so they don't overload the grid,
or because otherwise they'll generate too much
and there'll be problems at the other end of the park.
Claudia Isabee of Wimbledon writes the same thing,
and they have a very good windmill museum in Wimbledon.
- Today.
- It's on Wimbledon Common, it's right in the middle of the Common.
They've got an actual windmill, but it is good.
I've been in a few times.
- Have you?
- You do surprise me.
(laughing)
- And I got corrected.
I'm gonna put my hands up to it by Gaia Beck,
who said that the guy who built this first ever big wind turbine
was called Palmer Partner, and I said,
he lived near Grandpa's Nob Vermont in Cape Cod.
And Gaia Beck is just pointing out
that they are 386 miles apart.
So it's not near.
- Okay.
- Yeah, and I just didn't check my geography.
- Yeah.
- And I'll hold my hands up to that.
- That's fine.
- I think that's always to do with what your idea of scale is.
- Yeah, exactly, Gaia Beck.
- Yeah.
- If I'm living in Australia, you know, school was like,
it was ages away, but it didn't count as ages away.
It's just everything was ages away, right?
- I was thinking on a cosmic scale,
and I was saying they're incredibly near to each other.
- There you go.
That's move on, that's enough wind.
- Okay.
- Ooh, let's have a picture, get yourself off the hook.
- Great.
- Okay.
- Shuri Bluebond says, "I was just listening to an episode
of Little Fish, and someone just said that in the 1970s,
"there was a pet rock craze, and you would go to the store
"by googly eyes and put them on a rock."
- Okay.
- Would it have liked a pet rock?
- It was me who said that.
And I knew that I was kind of oversimplifying.
I think you could buy the actual,
you could buy a box for sure that said pet rock on it.
- Yeah.
- And I can't remember exactly how it worked.
- He's pretty got himself off the hook.
- Okay.
- You would buy a cardboard box with holes in it
that had a rock in it.
- Oh, so it did actually come with a rock.
- It came with a rock, yeah.
- Okay.
- And Shuri says, "You generally did not buy this for yourself.
"No kidding."
- Yeah, it's like a gag gift, right?
- Yeah, you bought it for someone else
and you couldn't just get a rock and put eyes on it.
That was considered really tacky and cheap.
- Yeah, but you know, we didn't all grow up in luxury.
- Like you did.
(laughing)
- Yeah, Shuri.
Are you saying that you were like
- Absolutely.
- Look, Shuri.
- We had pet dirt.
(laughing)
- Yeah, no, I mean, I mean fair, you know,
I think that's a fair cop.
- I wonder where they're all.
- Now, all the rocks.
- 'Cause you rarely go to someone's house
who say, "Oh, I got that rock in the '70s."
You know.
- Yeah.
- But they distributed.
Is someone collected them all
and's got like a rock graveyard.
- That's a great idea.
All right.
Now that one more gets us off off the hook,
then we're out of the corrections bit
and we're into the whimsical bit of the show.
- Oh, I love it.
- There's been the serious bit.
I'm so sorry, James.
- Is it me again?
- Oh, wow.
- So I have not been planning this.
- Let me get my heckles up.
- All right, Travis Roberts.
- Oh, yeah.
- In a recent episode, James noted
the only body part named after a woman
was a bit by the placenta.
- Yes, I still think that's true.
In fact, two weeks ago, I think,
or three weeks ago, on University Challenge,
they asked that same question and they said,
I think the answer was placenta.
- Oh, me.
- And they said the only body part named after a woman.
And I was delighted, of course,
because when you watch the University Challenge,
you usually get about one thing right,
but that's something I actually knew.
- You did write the questions for that episode, don't you?
- Okay, well, there is a mound of flesh by your thumb
on the palm, which is called apparently the mound of venus.
- Oh, is it really called that?
Or is that just what people call it?
But it's not the official name.
- Good point, don't know.
Sorry, it's the mound of venus.
But there's also the mound of venus,
which is down below for women.
- That feels like that definitely would be a slang word.
- That's a rude nickname.
- All right, well, I'm gonna go to Peter Wake's email
'cause you've definitely battered those two
back over the net.
Peter says, in the above episode, James Claim,
Bryser, is the only woman to have a body part named after her.
- What about the McConnell's capsula arteries,
which are named after EM McConnell,
who described them in a paper in 1953.
- Okay.
- I'm only aware of this because Edith Mavis McConnell
is my friend's late mother.
Isn't that good?
- Yes.
- She's EM McConnell.
- And she, like, people assume when they see EM,
because it's a few men.
- It's like EM Foster.
- It's EM Foster.
- Someone related to EM Foster.
- Yeah, and basically, the friend, Peter's friend,
saw an article where someone said,
oh, described by McConnell in his seminal work.
- Oh.
- And basically, it's a common mistake.
- I really like that.
I think I read this in New Scientist,
so they've made the mistake as well.
- They've made the mistake.
- But then I propagated it.
- But I think that's great.
I'd never heard of that person.
- Well, now, the small proportion of our audience
who subscribed to Club Fish will have had that myth busted.
- Yeah.
- Remember, McConnell's capsular arteries.
- Here you go.
- All right.
Children's ducking railings now.
- Okay.
- Oh, full hats.
- That's interesting.
- I can't remember when we mentioned this.
- I think I said that it happens that children
get stuck in railings and that you need to use olive oil
to get them out.
- Yes, yes.
- But we didn't have olive oil when I was a kid,
so they used facial oil butter or something.
- It was a little fish and we did it over Zoom.
And I then, it might not have made the show,
but I talked about how one of the members of Full House,
there was an urban legend that she stuck her head
through the bars at a theme park.
- Yes.
- And her head was knocked off by a passing roller coaster.
- That did make it.
That was very funny.
I wasn't in this one.
Yeah, yeah.
- But it was very sad because at the start of the day,
she was tall enough to ride all the rides over.
But at the end of the day, she was.
(laughing)
And what we're saying this is a thing
that you don't get anymore because of woke
is kids with their heads stuck through the railings.
- No, I actually said that that's, you know,
one day a kid's head fits in the railings
and then the next day it doesn't anymore.
- Well, we've had two solutions,
brilliant solutions proposed.
So Dave Woods points out that in reality,
the fire service approach is simply to lift the kid,
okay, so I've got my head through the railings, right?
The fire service simply lifts the kid's feet
above their head and then pushes their head
through the railings the other way
'cause then you're going through your ears, see what I mean?
- Right.
- So I've got through the problem is my ears, right?
It's stuck on my ears.
But if my feet are lifted above my head,
they can push my head back through the other way.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Brilliant.
- So it's like a way.
- It's like wheelbarrowing them out,
much like a dogfight, right?
- Exactly like a dogfight.
(laughing)
- My child's got stuck in the railings.
I can't remember.
- I put my figure up the bump on, what do I do?
(laughing)
- But who do you obligate to come
and they've got special fingers?
(laughing)
- This is great, this could be my book.
101 ways, a wheelbowering move.
Save your life, really good.
- Well, also James from Melbourne, right?
Save your olive oil.
A child's head does grow faster, right?
'Cause their head's grow faster.
But that means it does in fact have the largest
omnidirectional diameter of any part of their body.
This means they can just climb through the railing
by turning their chest sideways
and then climb back over if needed,
especially if you're a few floors up.
- That can't be true.
- I'm not going to climb into the full force
of the roller coaster, are you?
That makes no sense.
- I don't think that can possibly be true
that children who have got their head stuck
which does happen relatively often.
That they can all just turn their shoulders
around and walk through.
- That can't be true. - And you would think not.
I don't know.
For young children, baby's heads are bigger,
maybe than the rest of their body.
But we're talking about kids here.
- Yeah, it's usually kids who are around like 12,
11 or 12, but I see this in it.
- So I just don't know.
And also, if you're on the 10th floor,
you should not think, oh, that's fine.
Just climb through and then back over the top.
Don't do that. - Don't do that one.
- Yeah, yeah.
I think olive oil.
- Olive oil.
- Anyway, so thanks very much everyone.
We're solving problems together.
- Yeah, really good.
- Yeah.
- Matthias Panzenblut writes about Admin being a...
- Oh, well, I could see why you picked this one out.
(laughing)
- Why Admin is a common password?
- 'Cause it was mentioned at the show and Anna said,
"Oh, why is Admin as a cop?"
- Stupid password or something.
She said something, cutting like that.
Actually, it's because lots of devices come
with a default password, which is Admin,
and then no one changes the password.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- So that's in his bad practice, of course.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And that's the answer.
- Yeah.
I feel like that does a more...
- I'm sorry, but that's exactly why I thought it was the password.
I know you've seen the word Admin and thought,
we definitely need to get this email into the show, but...
(laughing)
'Cause it's one of your favorite things.
- Absolutely.
- So we don't think that's...
- No, I think most people would think
that Admin password would be the one that's default.
And less, for instance, Admin is one of your favorite things,
in which case you might put it as your password,
'cause you might put your wife's name as your password,
and you might just put Admin in,
'cause he loves Admin so much.
- Absolutely.
Well, Craig Taylor, a tech expert, ads,
that the, actually, a fun fact about this,
is the Admin in the password, is not,
because it was a shortened version of administrator,
but it was named after Iddi Admin,
the guy that you can't delete at the end of technology
in Uganda during Iddi Admin's dictatorship.
- I think we all need that, yeah.
(laughing)
- A bit of fun.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It's fun.
(laughing)
- Iddi Admin is an adagram of AI Admin.
- Oh my God.
I mean, I've definitely tried something I don't know from there.
- That's really good. - That's pretty good.
- Oh wow.
You've drawn a powerful connection there.
- Wow.
- Would you like one that's a bit visual,
but I haven't printed out the picture,
but I can get it on my phone.
- Yeah, sure.
- Eva Imbrus, right.
I just listened to the latest episode of Little Fish,
where you mentioned that a stadium in New Zealand
was built around a rock.
- Oh yeah.
- Oh yeah, this was one in Wellington, was it?
What was it?
Eden Park.
- Eden Park, that's it.
This reminded me of a supermarket in Veeamsea,
Estonia, where they built the supermarket
around a glacial boulder because it was too big to move.
Its diameter is 22 meters.
It's literally just in the middle of the aisles.
I don't know what you're thinking.
Can it be?
It absolutely is.
- Yeah.
- That's astonishing.
- That's great. - That's really good.
- I like when you saw that photo, you said it was astonishing,
which for Estonia feels like an Estonishing thing
would be Estonishing.
- You know what, I think that must have happened
in my head before I said it.
- That's really good.
You should send that to the Taurus bullage of Estonia.
- Get Estonished on this trip.
- Yeah.
- That should be in the airports as you arrive.
- You could also go, now you're talon like talking,
but it doesn't work spoken, but like on a poster,
it might work because talon looks a bit like talon.
Now you're talon.
- I think it's going to be a starter.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Let's go with this.
I always think if you just have two ideas,
then you can tell which one's the best.
- You can really force their hands to pick,
like we've got two ideas for you.
See which one you think is better.
(laughing)
- Estonishing or now you're talon.
- Imagine you come out of that meeting.
I can't believe they went with a talon.
(laughing)
We put it in only so that they choose the other one
and they've got with it.
(laughing)
- Estonio's got talon.
- That's quite good, actually.
- That's like the meeting shift to that one.
(laughing)
- It's talon Estonia.
- I thought it was Finland.
- Well, it's very close to Finland.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You could almost see Finland from it, but no.
- You're at the finish line.
(laughing)
- I thought people leaving Estonia for Finland.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I've got to say,
if the people at the Estonian tourist spot
aren't on the phone right now trying to procure our services,
they've made a big mistake.
- Absolutely, absolutely, yeah.
- We'll clip this out and send it to them.
Let's have a bit of fish life.
Madeline Chandler writes,
"I was delighted to hear you reference
"the giant pencil or the giant model of a pencil
"in Minneapolis in a recent episode."
- Oh yes, the one most like just a painted tree
or something, isn't it?
- Exactly, yeah.
- Especially as I'm currently seated,
50 yards from said pencil.
- As I write this thing.
- He is, isn't that great?
- That's cool.
- It's the Lake of the Isles pencil.
- 50 yards.
Now that is a good distance to say
if you're actually close to something.
It's not three in from 50 miles.
(laughing)
- Okay.
I was actually in attendance at the fifth annual sharpening
of the pencil earlier this year
and heard leading pencil sharpener David Reece
give a speech about the importance of pencils at the event.
And he wrote the book.
- The book, yeah.
- That's a sharp pencil.
- Oh my gosh.
- I know.
Interestingly, see what you think of this fact.
The home that the pencil stands in front of
was previously owned by Bobby McFerrin.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Don't worry, be happy, fake.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Although he was not involved in its creation.
- I think that's a down-level fact.
- Yeah.
- I think Dan Wood by that house.
(laughing)
- Absolutely, that's my kind of fact.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, that's very cool.
- Very cool.
- Ooh, this is a good bit.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
- Good.
(laughing)
- After two and a half years of doing this show.
Four, it's been four years.
- Four years, hasn't it?
- But it's only felt like two and a half.
- Well, welcome to the Mamba Lounge.
- Oh!
- Okay.
- We had so much great stuff about Mamba number five.
- Yeah.
- Fantastic.
- The shame Anna is not here.
'Cause it's her favorite song in the brain.
The only song she knows apart from the macarena.
(laughing)
- Eddie Edwards.
- Eddie the Eagle Edwards?
- Ooh, he doesn't say.
- Okay, it must be him.
- It must be actually,
'cause the quality of the email is so good.
- Yeah.
- I think it must be Eddie the Eagle writing.
In your recent discussion of Mamba number five,
it went unmentioned that Lou Beger's real name
is David Lou Beger, Balamese.
- I think I did actually mention that.
- You might have got cut, I didn't think so.
- No, it got in, but it was fleeting.
It was fleeting, but anyway,
Lou Beger is his middle name.
David Lou Beger, Balamese is his full name.
Which means, of course, that his stage name
is just a little bit of moniker.
- Oh, wow, yes.
Moniker with an I.k.a. - I am saying for the lesson though.
You know?
- Moniker is a word for a name, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Isn't that? - It's clever.
- It's nice.
Andy Sondin writes, did you know that Mamba number five,
wasn't the only Perez Prado originated single
to hit the UK charts in 1999?
- Ah.
- In fact, it wasn't the only Prado number
to hit the UK charts that fortnight.
- Was the other one the Guinness advert?
- The other one was Mucho Manbo Sway by Shaft.
Brackets, no, not that one.
But Mamba number five did better than it, right?
So that's, it's just interesting
that there was another Mamba win the charts
at the same time.
- Yeah, I can see that though.
Because Mamba number five was so massive,
I can see that everyone would want to jump
on the Mamba banwag.
- Do you think that was it?
- Yeah, possibly.
- People said, if you got that Mamba song,
they said, do you mean Mucho Manbo Sway by Shaft?
- What, that Shaft?
- No, not that one.
(laughing)
- Which one's that one?
- That one's from the movie, Isaac Hayes,
who was chef from South Park, wrote the theme tune
for a movie about an American detective via Cobb.
- It was like, shit, I'm here.
- Who's there someone who does the something?
- Duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh.
- Yes, lovely.
And one last one from Rachel Malcolm Swindles.
I'm confident I will not be the only person
to correct you on this, sorry Rachel,
but Nobel Prize winning author Gabrielle Garcia Marquez
only passed away in 2014.
- Okay.
- This, of course, means he could very reasonably
have enjoyed Lubega's Mamba number five
as his favourite Mamba number five
for the last 15 years of his life.
- Right.
- Because his favourite song was Mamba number five
and we said it was probably the original version.
- It definitely was the original, just to say.
- But he could have enjoyed.
- He could have, if he'd wanted to.
- Marquez's last noted publication was
"Memories of my melancholy haurs"
and was only published in 2005.
- I hope that's the four-legged animal you're talking about.
- I'm afraid not.
- Yeah.
- I did check and I don't believe there
are any characters named Angela Pamela Sanchez
or Rita.
- That's good.
- It's very, what a list of shit we have
who can leap from Marquez to Mamba.
- Stunning.
- All right, let's have a new section
- Cool.
- Really exciting.
So this is a matter of section.
Alan S. Miles writes "Long time emailer,
first time being read out."
- Which...
- Ah, he could write that in all of his emails.
- Exactly.
- No harm at all.
- Yeah.
- Very clever.
- Some spicy meat for you or perhaps Siemens gobbles.
So I'm gonna say this is a new section called spicy Siemens.
- Oh, Andy.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- No, I'll be tell that.
(laughing)
- What about meat squabbles?
- Meat squabbles.
That's the other half of the year.
- That's the other half of spicy Siemens.
- That's right.
Meat squabbles.
It sounds bad as well, actually, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
- It's going on and there.
- Just a meaty squabble.
- Yeah.
- How about Siemens meat?
- I just don't like any of these.
- Anyone watching or listening with a kid,
turn it off now.
- It's too late.
- It's too late, but do.
- Good advice, anyway, I think.
Maybe we should put that at the start of the show, yeah.
- Okay.
- It was a line recently, Andy read out an apology from Dan,
who had somehow managed to misremember his own name.
- Oh yeah.
(laughing)
- You remind us what?
- It was to do with my Chinese name,
and I said it was thank you, Uncle Egg,
but what I hadn't said in the show is that,
that needed the combination of my first name.
So my name is Sheerboard Dan,
which is thank you, Uncle Egg.
- All right.
- Sheerthank, or Uncle Dan Egg, brilliant.
Okay, so Alan points out,
given the stick Dan usually gets for dubious facts,
this didn't seem unreasonable.
However, further research was clearly required.
So after listening to the introductions
of all 644 episodes,
I discovered something surprising.
Despite his reputation,
Dan is the only member of the team,
never to have given a top of show apology
for something he has personally done.
He has apologized for poor sound quality,
for losing part of a show,
and even for losing an entire episode,
but never for one of his home facts.
(laughing)
By contrast, Andy and Anna
have both issued full factual retractions,
elephants and Leonardo da Vinci,
and James apologized for wording something poorly
regarding AST,
but in light of this evidence,
I think Dan's reputation deserves to be re-evaluated.
Statistically speaking,
he is the podcast's most reliable source.
- Is that what it means
if someone never apologizes for stuff?
(laughing)
When my wife says you never apologize,
I'm like, well, that's because I'm the most reliable
person in this relationship.
Okay, well, in future,
every time you get something wrong from now on,
the next episode,
we're gonna get you to do a reflection of that time.
- Well, you're gonna be hearing a lot from me, everyone.
(laughing)
- Well, let's go now to the Wankers Lounge,
which is an email from Rosemary Fotheringham,
who is our Wanker of the Weekend, okay.
- And I hope this isn't a mixture
between Simon Squabble's of Wankers Lounge,
but hello from Richland at Washington State.
- Lovely.
- Listen to this at the beginning, Club Fishman,
but first time right or inner,
I think I'm on my sixth or seventhary listen now.
- Wow. - It's extraordinary.
- Yeah, you do, whenever you hear that,
you just think we don't have nearly as many listeners
as we think we do.
- I think we've got like 200 listeners tops,
and they're all just playing it on repeat everywhere they go.
- Yeah.
- My husband and I even came all the way out to London
in 2024 to see you live at the Theatre Royal Drury Lane,
which was a dream come true.
- I wonder for us two.
- Absolutely.
- He's lovely to see you there.
- But why is this Wanker of the Week?
- Well, while I was that.
(laughing)
- Out on a recent trip to the Oregon coast along the way,
my husband and I knew that we simply had to make a pilgrimage
to Wankers Corner Saloon.
- Oh.
- We met up with a friend there who had just moved out to Portland.
She was equally delighted to go to a place called Wankers Corner
and told me she had made a point to visit
the Uranus Fudge Factory on her drive out to the West Coast.
- Oh.
- And Rosemary really excitingly got a menu
from Wankers Corner.
- Amazing.
- You come newspaper, sorry, not come.
It's a menu and newspaper from Wankers Corner.
- So we do need to remind people,
this was just a fact that came up on the show.
- Oh, sorry, yeah.
- There's a newspaper and it's named after Richard Wanker.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Wanker.
- No, Wanker.
Like Phil Wank.
- Yeah.
- But it's spelled Wanker.
- Yeah, but it says literally on the menu,
it says pronounce it Wankers.
- Wanker.
- Oh, I see, I wonder if that's maybe because they pronounce it
Wanker by mistake because it was named after
a guy called Richard Wanker.
- Oh, I do.
- He called himself Richard Wanker anyway.
- But yeah, there you go.
And she says, okay.
- We had a Wanker burger and a Wanker ale.
- A big, this, if I was looking straight away,
this would assume this was an Australia.
'Cause there's a lot of, there's two kangaroos
and an e-mew on this.
(laughing)
- I agree, that says Australia to me too.
And also it says Wanker all the way through it.
And but the other thing is this, it seems quite knowing.
I think it says, like are you a Wanker?
Grab your nuts.
You know, it's this, whoever has made this menu
has not accidentally got the name Wanker and thought,
oh, I don't know that this is rude.
- I think it would be funnier if you did do one
that's completely straight-laced.
- Agreed.
- We're proud Wankers and we want to welcome you
to the Wankers Saloon.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Very cool, but it's still fun.
That's very great.
- Yeah, very cool.
- So thank you for that Rosemary.
- Ooh, fish life.
- Did we already do that?
- Yeah, we did.
It was the woman who was sat next to the giant pencil.
- Ah, well we're going back to fish life now.
Lloyd Edwards writes about episode roughly 440.
So four years ago now.
- Okay.
- On a recent brackets in relation to the age of the universe
episode, thank you Lloyd.
(laughing)
- That's very funny.
- Yeah, you were discussing how Australian ab originals
used a small didgerie do-like instrument to lure emus
so they could harvest their eggs.
- Yeah, weird that we had emus in that Wankers corn thing
on the bigger emus now.
- 'Cause I did not plan that.
- No, you don't plan any of this, do you?
- I didn't even print the picture of the rock out for you.
(laughing)
- During this segment, James mentioned that emus
have been said to react if you lay on your back
with your foot in the air.
- Yes, I remember it.
- Yes.
I'm pleased to say I was able to test this hypothesis today.
(laughing)
It was hugely successful.
Oh, I was like the snake charmers of old.
Their head and eyes followed my foot hypnotically.
And when I lowered my foot and stood up,
they responded angrily.
(laughing)
Thankfully, they were behind a fence.
So I remain unmolested.
- Oh, okay.
- Boy, that was.
- That's good.
- Isn't that good?
- Nice.
I was hoping that ended.
I'm still here, please send someone.
(laughing)
- I am now the king.
- Only as long as I remain upside down
with my foot in the air.
(laughing)
That's great.
It's always good to hear your facts,
which when you read them out,
you probably slightly doubt them yourself
turning out to be true.
- Yeah, that's super cool.
- That's really cool.
So that's a good thing for anyone encountering an emu.
That's how to get them on your side.
Andrea M has just been listening to Little Fish
and a fact about the West Edmonton Mall in Canada
and the submarines.
- Yeah.
- Remember this?
- I do.
- The submarines.
I worked as a full-time scuba diver
at the mall for a summer.
- Wow.
- Our main job was being on call to rescue stuck submarines.
- Oh, because you said that they didn't get...
No, you said, I think you said no one had died.
- I said no one had died.
I did not say they'd never got stuck.
- No.
- Because at times they got stuck all the time.
Apparently you could be as young as 15
driving one of these submarines.
- Wow.
- You could be able to speak to me.
- They're not like, they're not like Trident.
Are they?
They're like little fun.
- They're not armed.
- Yeah, they're on subs.
- Well, there are people in them anyway.
But occasionally one of the undrivers would steer off course
and once they were off the course,
they couldn't get back on.
And members of the public don't really like getting stuck
in small spaces underwater.
We had to rush over to the lake,
get into Wetsuit, throw on our scuba gear
and get into the water
and physically manipulate the sub back onto course.
- Wow.
- I know.
- It's like a Mario Kart when you go off
and that cloud fishes you back into the...
- Into the course.
- Andrea M. was that cloud.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I was the first woman employed full time as a diver
back at about 1991.
- Wow.
Trailblazer as well.
- Yeah.
- She says I was overqualified being the only one
with a rescue diver certificate.
(laughing)
- Raises questions about everyone else.
- It is sucking that as a rescue diver.
- Also, interesting they don't have someone just
in a suit waiting for that to happen.
So I guess it doesn't happen as much.
But still, if you're claustrophobic,
you've gone of course in your stug.
In fact, that someone has to get down there.
- But there's a 15-year-old kid
like a child who's like, "Ah, sorry, sorry."
- I was sending someone down now
they're just gonna get changed.
They go to like, on their way over,
at which point they will start putting on their scuba gear.
- Yeah.
- Which is not a rapid process, is it?
- No.
- I don't know.
They might have one of those like Fireman's poles
where you go down and you land into your scoop.
- Oh, like Batman's lovely idea.
- That's a lovely idea.
And that would slow you to a halt as well,
'cause it's very frictiony, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Anyway, thank you Andrea.
What a thing to be able to get Nemo from.
She says, "I do occasionally still pull out.
"I worked as a scuba diver in a shopping mall
"during a game of two truths and a lie."
- Very good.
- Oh, we should play that game.
- We should.
- Not now.
- I was lying.
(laughing)
- Damn it.
- Ooh, extreme fish.
- Oh yeah.
- This is a thing, very exciting.
Jake Clements has written in,
"Is this the first time Andy
"has ever had a man detained?"
- Nope.
(laughing)
- This is a World Cup thing.
- Basically, there is a football fan,
apparently a semi-famous football fan.
- Oh, I know who you're talking about.
- Andy Mill?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Right.
- He like always carries around a plastic World Cup
and he's got quite a distinctive face.
- Okay.
- And wherever England, a play and football
and they need to interview a fan,
he always pops up.
I think he's written a buck about the World Cup.
- I know who tongue mounts.
- Yeah, nice.
I'm not familiar with his work,
but it turns out he is familiar with mine.
- Oh yeah.
- So he was on his way into a World Cup match in America.
- And the guards stopped him,
'cause they were going through everyone's,
just looking at everyone's bags and things.
And they found he had a book on him called
"A Beginner's Guide to Breaking and Entering."
- Oh, way.
- And he got hauled off into a side room
and interrogated him.
- Oh, way.
- By two goons.
- What for ages?
- 15 minutes.
- Fit must have felt long though.
- For them, if they had to read the buck.
(laughing)
- Yeah, and then eventually their boss turned up
and said, "This is clearly a novel.
"This is not a security risk," and he was released.
And yeah, Andy might want to use Mill
on the blurb of his next book.
He described it as just a novel.
(laughing)
- Just a novel.
- That's very interesting.
- So anyway, that was very funny.
Thanks, but no thanks.
- Yes, please.
- Nick writes, I said that word, didn't I?
- It's like you're about to say a surname
and then you realize you weren't allowed.
- Yes, but he actually hasn't included a surname
as far as I know.
- Okay.
- But Nick writes.
Maybe a surname's rights.
(laughing)
- Nick writes, "Another society to join Andy?"
Question mark.
With details of the British water tower appreciation society,
which has spent 20 years championing Britain's water towers.
- Okay.
- With exhibitions, tours, lectures, and media appearances.
Now, sadly, their chairman, secretary,
and treasurer are stepping down together.
Feels like something's happened.
- It does really, doesn't it?
It feels like some dodgy water tower
isn't happening.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Three new officers to keep it going.
They have a healthy bank balance,
hundreds of members, and hard one trust
with tower owners and heritage bodies.
How hard one can the trust be?
But okay.
But without new leadership,
they'll have to wind up the society.
- Okay.
- Time for someone to step forwards.
Thanks for being with that in there.
Thanks, but thanks.
- No, I don't mind you doing that instead of this.
I mean, only 'cause it's your calling,
we would miss you obviously.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You know.
- No, I get it.
- I think, you know, follow your heart.
- Yeah, okay, well that's what I wanted to do.
(laughing)
- Did you pause on Nick
'cause you thought, hang on to James Wright this email.
(laughing)
- You just trying to lure me into question.
- I basically spent the last two weeks scouring
the job pages of the newspaper,
trying to fight things for you.
- I'm up for it.
I am up for it.
- No, thank you very much.
- Nick.
- Catfish corner.
- Okay.
- Use action.
- This is someone pretending to be a listener,
but isn't actually...
(laughing)
- Peter Dexan of Dorchester writes,
"I believe it is James who feeds his feline housemate,
"Evian Water."
- Yeah.
- "Does he know that Stanley Kubrick
"also fed his cats, Evian Water?"
- I did not know that.
- That's something you two haven't...
- Is that true?
- Something you two can talk about now.
(laughing)
- Yeah, well Peter includes a source
from a book by a guy called Ian Watson
and a page number.
- Wow.
- And a title.
- Yeah, page number and titles.
I haven't checked, but.
- How interesting.
- Ian Watson worked with Stanley Kubrick writing AI.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Do you remember that was a movie?
- Oh, okay.
- He died in the process of it being made
and Spielberg took over.
- Was that with...
- It was a little kid and a...
- There's someone very famous.
Wasn't it Robin Williams or...
- No, it was one of the bison teniel, man.
- Okay, but there was a...
- There's a famous person in it.
- Yeah, I can't remember who now.
- Is it weird to Spielberg?
- Isn't it weird that we're discussing AI admin again?
- It is weird.
(laughing)
- Okay, that's really...
I'm glad that someone else has followed my lead.
I assume I did it first and then Kubrick
from beyond the grade.
- Definitely.
(laughing)
- Just on bullying and workplace relations on the show.
- Oh.
- Oh, okay, this is why we've been brought here today as well.
- Yeah, I'm afraid so.
- All right.
- Beth writes in, "I'm glad the bullying of Andy
has been widely unpopular,
but do understand your need for lively
and mildly antagonistic banter.
While everyone bullying Andy feels uncomfortable
and a bullying Dan is familiar reassuring and entertaining.
Could clips of the latter be spliced in
wherever you would previously had a sprinkling of the former?
I'm sure the inbox is full of this suggestion,
but thought I'd be one of the thousands to send it, is.
(laughing)
- So every time we feel like saying something
antagonistic towards you,
we just stop and play in a clip of Anna.
I'm really not done.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
- I mean James, you do the edits, is it workable?
- Um, we'll need to get Anna in here
to slag you off a few times so that I have the material.
- So you mean fresh stuff.
- Yeah.
- Maybe if you and her can sit in a room for a day or so
and she just lays into you.
- I shouldn't handle a day in a room with me.
(laughing)
Probably get enough from half an hour.
- Yeah.
Fair enough.
All right.
- Well, we better wrap up.
We better.
- Oh, we should.
- The next time you hit Drop of the Line everyone,
just to brace yourself, it's gonna be live.
We're recording one live at the London Podcast Festival
and I think it's going to be a very weird
and uncomfortable show.
- It's not impossible that it's so weird and uncomfortable
that we don't put it out and we record another one
in the office.
- That is a great point.
- Yeah.
- So look out for that.
If the next one you hear is us here again,
something's gone so badly wrong.
(laughing)
All we've decided is just better for the room, you know.
It's gonna be weird reading the emails out in front of people,
some of whom will have written the emails
that we're reading out.
If the next episode is in the office
and it's me, Dan and Anna,
then something's gone so wrong in that live show
that Andy has decided to work for the Water Tower Company.
(laughing)
- So this could be it for my time on this beach.
And I just want to say thank you.
It's been a wonderful four years.
- It's been great.
- I hope you guys have enjoyed today's show.
Don't please just...
- Okay, sorry.
- Okay, no, go on.
- No, no, it has been fun.
If it's your last show, we might as well say it.
Yeah, you've done it.
If it is my last show and you just say, "Yeah, it has been fun."
I think that's an incredibly underwhelming goodbye.
- If it is your last show,
I would like to say that you have done a job.
- You have been here.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- That's it for this episode of Drop of the Line.
It's been a joy.
It's the most meaningful thing I do every fortnight.
So to keep it meaningful, please send an email
to podcast@asign.com.
Go out, go out strong on your final app.
- Just think of all those emails
that people are sending to podcastatui.com
that you're not getting.
- I used to know a bloke whose email was,
I won't say it's full email,
but it was Craig @at something @asign.
Something else.
His life was at nightmare.
His life was an absolute nightmare.
- Yeah.
So, to clarify, it's podcast@asignqy.com.
That's the email address to send it, it's not.
- It's not for the listeners, it's not podcast@asignqy.com.
It's just @, you can just say @, okay.
- We're that far into the internet now that I think.
- Okay, someone's confident.
Sorry, Mr. Gates.
- It's the most recent internet person I can think of.
- Well, nailed it.
Say bye now.
(laughing)
- Bye now.
- Oh no, it doesn't.
- Absolutely nailed that one, guys.
(upbeat music)